so now let's look at the performance of
move Z and move and type of in if
conversion in the previous quiz we have
already seen that branch code like this
can be if converted into code like this
let's suppose that this Branch here is
perfectly predicted so all we have to
worry about is this one and let's say
that this branch is 80% accurately
predicted and let's say there is a 40
instruction penalty on mispredictions in
that case we have here this cost us four
instructions this costs us three
instructions on this path or two
instructions on this path let's say it's
a very difficult to predict Branch so
it's not
biased in which case we have 2.5
instructions all the time plus 20% of
the time we have a 40 instruction
penalty this gives us on average 10.5
instructions worth of work on this
versus four here so obviously the if
converted code is more optimal